[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":92406,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":94160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":8960,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":103122,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":16874,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":119998,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1923,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":121923,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5126,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":127050,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1347,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":128398,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your  result.) ","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":14298,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":142697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1312,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":144011,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6967,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":150979,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 =  2 becaus e 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1188,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":152168,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3467,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":155636,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1878,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":157515,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the  first n umber, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3157,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":160673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1217,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":161891,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3011,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":164902,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":2170,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":167073,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3000,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":170073,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1214,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":171288,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3395,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":174684,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1462,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":176147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, yo u subtra ct 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2829,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":178977,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1285,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":180263,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":1752,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":182018,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":69869,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":251887,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":9247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":261135,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":21572,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":282708,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4540,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":287249,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1560,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":288810,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"Wha t is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3093,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":291903,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1197,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":293101,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["14","1","4"],"rt":5506,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":298608,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1059,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":299667,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":5364,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":305032,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4584,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":309617,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":31018,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":340636,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i>  under +< sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":35901,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":376538,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":7852,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":384391,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1553,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":385945,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3362,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":389309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1660,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":390970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a  generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2949,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":393921,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1224,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":395146,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":3254,"trial_type":"questi on","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":398401,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1233,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":399636,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to com plete th e remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":26641,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":426278,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7452,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":433732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":4409,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":438141,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3146,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":441288,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is  7 +<sub> 9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4587,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":445875,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4144,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":450020,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6384,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":456406,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2957,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":459363,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"4+1 equals 5 which is less than 9 so no change needed","response_history":["4+1 equals 5 which is less than 9 so no change needed"],"rt":22885,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":482250,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"8+4 =12 so I need to subtract 9 which equals 3","response_history":["8+4 +","8+4 =12 so no change","8+4 =12 so no chang","8+4 =12 so no chan","8+4 =12 so no cha","8+4 =12 so no ch","8+4 =12 so no c","8+4 =12 so no ","8+4 =12 so no","8+4 =12 so n","8+4 =12 so I need to subtract 0","8+4 =12 so I need to subtr act 9 wh ich eaque","8+4 =12 so I need to subtract 9 which eaqu","8+4 =12 so I need to subtract 9 which eaq","8+4 =12 so I need to subtract 9 which eauals","8+4 =12 so I need to subtract 9 which eaual","8+4 =12 so I need to subtract 9 which eaua","8+4 =12 so I need to subtract 9 which eau","8+4 =12 so I need to subtract 9 which ea","8+4 =12 so I need to subtract 9 which eque","8+4 =12 so I need to subtract 9 which equals 3"],"rt":34346,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":516597,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"I have no idea ","response_history":["I have no idea "],"rt":37233,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":553830,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"f ree","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":9763,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":563597,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4161,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":567760,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":10569,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":578330,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6  I need to make it equal 9 so that it will come out to 0","response_history":["6  I need to make it ew","6  I need to make it equal 9 so that it will come out to 0"],"rt":21945,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":600276,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No because you can't create every number with 2 123456789 for example ","response_history":["yes becasue you can creat ","yes becasue you can create","No ecaue","No ecau","No eca","No ec","No e","No because you can't create every number with 2 123456789 for example "],"rt":48487,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":648764,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"fr ee","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes because you can generate every number with 3 123456789","response_history":["Yes becasue","Yes becasu","Yes becas","Yes because you can generate eveyr n","Yes because you can generate eveyr ","Yes because you can generate eveyr","Yes because you can generate evey","Yes because you can generate eve","Yes because you can generate every number with 3 123456789"],"rt":21835,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":670600,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No  because you can't create every number with 5 123456789 ","response_history":["No  because you cna't ","No  because you cna't","No  because you cna'","No  because you cna","No  because you cn","No  because you cant","No  because you can't r","No  beca use you  can't creat eve","No  because you can't creat ev","No  because you can't creat e","No  because you can't creat ","No  because you can't creat","No  because you can't create ee","No  because you can't create every number with 65","No  because you can't create every number with 6","No  because you can't create every number with 5 123456789 "],"rt":27482,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":698083,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because you can't create every number with 6 ","response_history":["no becaue you ","no becaue you","no becaue yo","no becaue y","no becaue ","no becaue","no because you can 't ","no because you can 't","no because you can '","no because you can ","no because you can","no because you can't r","no because you can't creat ever","no be cause yo u can't creat eve","no because you can't creat ev","no because you can't creat e","no because you can't creat ","no because you can't create every number with 6 "],"rt":42736,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":740821,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":671830,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1412652,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":18276,"trial_type":"questio n","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1430931,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I have no idea to be honest ","response_history":["I have no idea to be hones ","I have no idea to be honest "],"rt":14222,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1445155,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I have no idea I am not good at math","response_history":["I have no idea I am not good at math"],"rt":15446,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1460603,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":9665,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1470270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":7218,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1477489,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":94913,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1572404,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I have no idea to how to solve or explain ","response_history":["I have noid","I have noi","I have no idea to how to solve or explain "],"rt":30486,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1602892,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Som etimes"],"rt":103770,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1706665,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I have no idea I was just guessing ","response_history":["I have no idea I ws ","I have no idea I ws","I have no idea I w","I have no idea I a","I have no idea I was just guessing "],"rt":19321,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1725990,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Ne ver","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":13837,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1739829,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2100,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1741930,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"33","response_history":["33"],"rt":2986,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1744917,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2544,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1747462,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Calculus at college level but I barley passed and had to take it 2","response_history":["Calcu","Calc","Calcul","Calcu","Calc","Calculs ","Calculus  ","Calculus at college level bt","Calculus at college level b","Calculus at college level but I bareley ","Calculus at college level but I bareley","Calculus at college level but I barele","Calculus at college level but I barel","Calculus at college level but I bare","Calculus at college level but I barly passed and Hd","Calculus at college level but I barly passed and H","Calcul us at co llege level but I barly passed and had to take it 2","Calculus at college level but I barley passed and had to take it 2"],"rt":40889,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1788352,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":6058,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1794412,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen  it used  or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3861,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1798273,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":6450,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1804725,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":4376,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1809102,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3392,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1812495,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2195,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1814690,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English ","response_history":["English "],"rt":6306,"trial_type":"questio n","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1820997,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes ","response_history":["yes "],"rt":5091,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1826090,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"sorry if I did poorly I really did try","response_history":["sorry ofi ","sorry ofi","sorry of","sorry o","sorry if I did poorly I really did try"],"rt":10824,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1836916,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]